[JOHN WILLIAMS' "THE IMPERIAL
MARCH" PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
(Leonard:)Will you please turn your shirt off?
(Raj:)What? I'm giving myself
dramatic entrance music.
(Raj:)People will know I'm awesome
and to be feared.
(Howard:)Right. There's nothing more awesome
and frightening...
(Howard:)...than a man who's got music blasting
from between his nipples.
[MUSIC STOPS]
(Leonard:)-Hey, Stuart. What's going on?
-Well, you might wanna mark...
(Stuart:)...your Google calendars. Stan Lee
is coming to do a signing on Thursday.
(Sheldon:)Did he finally write a sequel
to his autobiography?
(Sheldon:)I'm sure ages 79 through 87
were just action-packed.
(Stuart:)No, just a regular comic signing.
(Stuart:)My uncle is his dermatologist,
and Stan's doing him a favor.
Oh, I don't wanna know that.
(Sheldon:)How can I possibly discuss with
Stan Lee the scientific foundations...
...for interstellar flight on a surfboard
when part of my brain...
(Sheldon:)...will be scanning his face
for signs of contagious skin disease?
(Leonard:)Stan Lee does not have
a contagious skin disease.
(Sheldon:)Well, look who thinks
he's Stuart's uncle now.
(Raj:)Can't believe it.
We're gonna meet Stan Lee.
[THE POINTER SISTERS' "I'M SO
EXCITED" PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
(Raj:)I'm so excited
And I just can't hide it
I'm about to lose control
And I think I like it
(Howard:)I'm sad to say
I taught him those moves.